Narrator: Prefixes and suffixes
Prefixes
M: a / an means ‘without’: amoral, anaemic
Narrator: 2
F: ante means ‘before’: antenatal
Narrator: 3
M: circum means ‘around’: circumnavigate
Narrator: 4
F: contra / contro means ‘against’: contradict, controversial
Narrator: 5
M: extra means ’beyond’, ‘more than’: extraordinary
Narrator: 6
F: fore means ‘before’: foresee
Narrator: 7
M: homo means ‘the same’: homogenous
Narrator: 8
F: hyper means ‘over’, ‘above’: hyperactive
Narrator: 9
M: infra means ‘beneath’, ‘below’: infrastructure
Narrator: 10
F: macro means ‘large’: macroeconomics
Narrator: 11
M: micro means ‘small’: microscope
Narrator: 12
F: omni means ‘all’, ‘every’: omnipotent
Narrator: 13
M: para means ‘beside’: paramedic
Narrator: 14
F: trans means ‘across’: transatlantic
Narrator: 15
M: uni means ‘one’: unicorn